Welcome to the world and
the awe inspiring realm of
hardware acceleration,
a universe where innovation
is limitless and holds no
boundaries.
We ventured into crafting
a groundbreaking RISC V
processor armed with a
matrix Mac unit.
Stepping into the arena with
powerhouses like Tesla,
Firepro and Intel,
each fuelling innovation
in its own distinctive manner.
Ponder upon the autonomous
vehicle.
An extraordinary marvel of
this vehicle with its state
of the art cameras and sensors,
identifies obstructions,
tracks its surroundings,
and guarantees secure
transit.
It stands as a compelling
testament to the vast and
limitless potential of hardware
acceleration in practical
applications.
Inside the Tesla Giga
factory, we catch a glimpse
of an advanced world taking
shape.
From self driving vehicles
to humanoid robots, video,
and AI driven autonomous
entities, the need for hardware
accelerators like RISC five
processors is more palpable
than ever.
What does the future of computing
look like?
Its guided by a RISC five
matrix Mac processor, an
extraordinary innovation
beyond the usual chip
implemented on an FPGA.
It manages structure, control,
and data hazards with new
techniques.
Our processor deftly navigates
through these hazards.
Its a symphony of efficiency
and performance.
Moving from the processor,
we journey into the domain
of the urat transceiver,
a marvel built by our very
own hands.
The GDS two file has
already been sent for
fabrication.
A significant stride forward.
This will mark the creation
of our university's first
ever fabricated chip.
With lightning fast transmission
speeds, our UART
transceiver ensures real
time communication.
The heart of our processor
lies the Matrix Mac
module, a revolutionary
edition that revolutionizes
matrix manipulation.
It enables efficient matrix
operations like multiplication,
addition, and
subtraction.
With the Matrix Mac module,
our processor transcends
limitations, opening doors
to new possibilities.
Our RISC five processor,
already capable of handling
over 20 instructions,
now boasts an additional
ten instructions.
This means it can manage
more complex computations
and tackle diverse tasks
with ease.
This and the instruction
set is a leap forward in
computational capability,
setting new standards in
performance and versatility.
But how does our processor
orchestrate this symphony
of computation?
Instructions carefully
constructed travel to our
UART transceiver
receiving they land in the
instruction memory.
The processor then executes
each instruction with precision,
guiding us to a brighter
future in the computing world.
Our journey doesnt end here.
We have grand plans for the
future.
We aim to convert our RISCV
processor into a system on
chip, a single integrated
circuit that can perform
all the functions of a computer
system.
But were not stopping there
were also developing an online
simulator that will be accessible
to the whole world.
This will allow everyone
from students to professionals,
to test our product and
experience its power
firsthand.
So join us as we continue
to push the boundaries of
what's possible in computing,
and together we can shape
the future of this industry.